CONTACT

- valentinamarenda1@gmail.com
- + 54 (0221) 15-5716173
- La Plata Buenos Aires Argentina
- 10/18/1990
- in /valentinamarenda
- /valenmarenda

SKILLS WEB DEVELOPMENT

THIML

Js JavaScript

3 CSS

React JS

San SASS

NySQL

◆ GIT

Php PHP

G GITHUB

node® Node JS

Mongo DB Firebase

OTHERS SKILLS

- Microsoft office
- Google ads facebook ads

LANGUAGE

Level: C1 - Advanced

VALENTINA MARENDA

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

I've worked in marketing and sales for several years, until I discovered that web development was my vocation, hence why I decided to study programming.

I am currently a web developer seeking to learn more about this vast profession. I am studying full stack web development, close to finishing it. I am also doing courses on C#, .net, and databases to complement my knowledge.

My goal is to be part of a company that will allow me to continue to grow professionally as a programmer.

EDUCATION

- Full Stack Development: includes the courses:
- React Js
- JavaScript
- Web development
- Backend development

Coderhouse 2020- In progress

Course: C# .net

Udemy 2021 - In progress

• Course: Web development HTML5, CSS3, JS AJAX PHP y MySQL.

Udemy 2020 - Finished

· Course: Social media management & digital marketing

Start digital School 2019 - Finished

Course: Coaching & leadership

FCA 2019 - Finished

· Course: Academic english

(8 months in Dublin, Irlanda) - Chapter House Irlanda - Finished

WORK EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer 2021 - present

- Ecommerce website development

Web developer freelance 2021 - present

Website development for institutions and companies

React JS tutor 2021 - present

Coder House

- Checking and assessing student work
- Planning, preparing and delivering after class lessons

Mentor 2021 - present

Nucba

- Checking and assessing student work
- Planning, preparing and delivering class lessons

Marketing and sales manager 2019 - 2021

Hotel - Head of marketing and Sales

- Development of sales, marketing and advertising strategies. Marketing planning
- Social media management.
- Set up sales rates. Competitor analysis. Intermediary with companies
- Coordination of business events and group bookings
- Personnel in charge

Marketing and sales manager 2014 - 2019

Este University

Head of Marketing and publicity

- Development of marketing and advertising strategies.
- Social media management
- Analysis and development of facebook ads, google ads and google analytics